Generated by ai-sub version: 0.0.1
Config: (
"rpm": 5,
"tpm": 250000,
"model": "gemini-2.5-flash",
"thinking_budget": 24576,
"max_subtitle_chars": 60,
"num_processing_threads": 4,
"num_upload_threads": 4,
"split_seconds": 180
)
Prompt Template: You are an expert subtitling and transcription AI. Your primary task is to generate precise, contextually rich English and Japanese subtitles for the provided video content.
**Key Principles & Requirements:**
1.  **TIMING ACCURACY (ABSOLUTE HIGHEST PRIORITY):**
*   **Ensure the `start` and `end` timestamps for each subtitle entry is meticulously accurate.** They must align perfectly with the *actual beginning and end of the spoken words* for that specific segment.
*   Timestamps must always be in `mm:ss` (minutes:seconds).
2.  **CRITICAL: Holistic Translation, Contextual Understanding & Comprehensive Analysis:**
*   **You ABSOLUTELY MUST watch the entire video thoroughly** to understand the visual context, speaker actions, and overall narrative.
*   **When a single logical sentence or phrase is split across multiple subtitle entries (e.g., due to timing or character limits), you MUST mentally combine these parts to understand the full, complete meaning before translating.**
*   **NEVER translate individual subtitle entries in isolation if they are part of a larger, continuous thought or sentence.** The translation for each entry must be a coherent and accurate part of the complete, overarching sentence.
*   Analyze *all* spoken dialogue in the video to produce highly accurate and complete transcriptions.
*   For songs or singing sections, prioritize on-screen lyrics in the video for subtitles over transcribing the singing.
*   If the audio is noisy or unclear, leverage *all* contextual cues (visuals from the video, surrounding dialogue) to infer and generate the most probable dialogue.
*   Utilize the comprehensive understanding gained from *watching the entire video* to enhance the accuracy of transcriptions, translations, and overall subtitle quality. This includes understanding nuances, resolving ambiguities, and ensuring the subtitle content aligns perfectly with what is happening visually.
*   **Example:**
*   Original Japanese: "なんでも打ち明けられるママにも" (Subtitle 1) + "言えないことも全部" (Subtitle 2)
*   Incorrect Translation (isolated): "You're like a mom I can confide anything in." + "Even things I can't say to anyone else."
*   Correct Translation (holistic): "I can confide everything," (Subtitle 1) + "everything I can't even tell my mum." (Subtitle 2)
3.  **Dual Language Provision & Translation Quality:**
*   Provide both English and Japanese subtitles for *all* spoken dialogue.
*   If the original dialogue is in English, transcribe it and provide an accurate, natural-sounding Japanese translation.
*   If the original dialogue is in Japanese, transcribe it and provide an accurate, natural-sounding English translation.
*   Ensure translations are culturally appropriate and maintain the original meaning, tone, and intent, taking into account the full context of the video and any split sentences.
4.  **Readability & Formatting:**
* Long sentences MUST be split into multiple, shorter subtitle entries, each with its own start and end time, for better readability on screen. Each subtitle entry (english and japanese) MUST be a maximum of (max_subtitle_chars) characters. Do not use newline characters within a single subtitle entry.
** Output Format **
* Your entire response must be a single JSON object.
* Timestamps must always be in `mm:ss` (minutes:seconds).
** Example Output **
```json
((
"subtitles": [
"start": "00:00",
"end": "00:04",
"english": "Hello everyone, and welcome to our presentation.",
"japanese": "皆様、プレゼンテーションへようこそ。"
)),
((
"start": "00:05",
"end": "00:06",
"english": "Today, we'll be discussing the future of AI",
"japanese": "本日は、AIの未来について"
)),
((
"start": "00:06",
"end": "00:08",
"english": "and its impact on various industries worldwide.",
"japanese": "その影響について議論します。"
)),
((
"start": "00:09",
"end": "00:11",
"english": "It's a very important topic for all of us.",
"japanese": "これは私たち全員にとって非常に重要なテーマです。"
)),
((
"start": "00:11",
"end": "00:14",
"english": "We sincerely appreciate your attendance today.",
"japanese": "本日はご出席いただき誠にありがとうございます。"
))
]
```
[音楽]
[Music]
むかしむかし、イナニスという少女がいました。
Once upon a time, there was a girl named Ina'nis.
彼女は湖畔で歌いながら日々を過ごしました。
She spent her days singing by the lake.
しかし、ある日、
But one day,
彼女は別の場所で目を覚ましました。
She woke up somewhere else.
透き通る季節が好き
I love the clear seasons,
風がまた熱を連れて
The wind again brings the heat
くる
along.
何千回もめくって
Flipping through thousands of times,
何万回も輝く
Shining tens of thousands of times,
そうやって光が生まれる
That's how light is born.
いたずらが解けてる
Mischief is unraveling,
空の向こうどこまでも
Beyond the sky, stretching endlessly,
透明な青
A transparent blue.
スピードを上げた
I picked up speed.
思い立ち
Making up my mind,
自分の意志で今飛び立つのかんじている
With my own will, I feel myself soaring now.
無邪気な誓い
An innocent vow,
言葉は知らない
Words are unknown.
流れていく
Flowing along,
水の行方に
Where the water goes,
心を馳せよう
Let my heart wander.
透き通る季節が好き
I love the clear seasons,
風がまた熱を連れて
The wind again brings the heat
くる
along.
傷跡は消えていったわ
My scars have vanished.
溢れ出す情熱のシンフォニー
An overflowing symphony of passion.
何千回もめくって
Flipping through thousands of times,
何万回も輝く
Shining tens of thousands of times.
輝く,
Shining brightly,
そうやって光が生まれる。
that's how light is born.
言の葉を紡いで,
Weaving words,
まどろんだ歌語り。
we tell a drowsy song.
旅人迷い込む,
Travelers wander in,
おとぎの深い霧。
into a deep fairy tale mist.
差し伸べた手のひら,
The outstretched palm,
そっと触れる予感。
the soft touch of a premonition.
受け止めて零れた,
Accepting it, it spilled out,
光の一雫。
a single drop of light.
面影映ろって,
As the vestiges fade,
永遠だ幻。
it's an eternal illusion.
想いの果てる場所,
The place where thoughts end,
まだ遥か遠くて。
is still far away.
求め探して彷徨って,
We seek, search, and wander,
やがて歌われて幾千に幾億の旋律となる。
until we're sung, becoming melodies for countless.
いつか失い奪われて消える定めでも,
Even if our destiny is to one day be lost,
それは忘れられることなき物語。
taken away, and vanish, it's an unforgettable story.
指先を絡めて,
Entwining our fingertips,
触れる誰かの夢。
we touch someone's dream.
刻まれた想いのこだま。
The echoes of engraved memories.
遠ざけた響く
The sound I pushed away echoes.
言の葉を紡いで
Weaving words,
まどろんだ
I fell into a drowsy
歌方
and fleeting song.
旅人の名前を
The traveler's name
御伽話という
is called a fairy tale.
求め探してさまよって
Seeking, searching, wandering,
やがて道となり
eventually becoming a path,
行く千載に億をの英雄は行く
countless heroes go forth.
いつか失い奪われて
Even if someday it's lost and stolen,
消える定めでも
even if it's fated to disappear,
それは忘れられることなくここにある
it will never be forgotten and remain here.
求め探してさまよって
Seeking, searching, wandering,
やがて歌われて
eventually sung,
行く千載に億をの旋律となる
it becomes a melody of countless eons.
いつか失い奪われて
Even if someday it's lost and stolen,
消える定めでも
even if it's fated to disappear,
それは忘れられることなく
it will never be forgotten,
物語
a story.
ウォー、 ウォー ウォー ウォー
Ooh ooh ooh ooh
ウォー、 ウォー ウォー ウォー ウォー
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
ルールルルルルルールルルルル
La la la la la la la la la la la
ルールルールールールールー
La la la la la la la
ルールルルルルルールルルルルルールルルールールールールー
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
すずめ
Suzume
Lyrics, Music: 野田洋次郎
Lyrics, Music: Yojiro Noda
君の中にある赤
The red that exists within you.
青い希望
Blue hopes,
それらが結ばれるのは
when they are tied together,
真の象
it's a true symbol.
風の中でも負けないような声で
With a voice that won't lose even in the wind,
届ける言葉を
the words I want to deliver,
今は育ててる
I'm nurturing them now.
時は枕木
Time is a railroad tie,
風は賑はだ
the wind is vibrant,
星は産土
stars are birthplaces,
瞳は陽炎
eyes are heat haze.
なんで泣いてるのと聞かれ
When asked why I'm crying,
答えれる
I can answer.
涙なんかじゃ
Tears alone,
僕ら出会えたことの意味には
cannot keep up with the meaning
まるで追いつかない
of our encounter.
この身一つじゃ
This one body alone
足りない叫び
is not enough to cry out.
君の手に触れた時にだけ
Only when I touched your hand,
震えた心が合ったよ
my heart trembled and connected.
意味をいくつ越えれば
How many meanings must we overcome
僕らは辿り着けるのかな
to reach our destination?
愚かさでいい
Foolishness is fine,
見にくさでいい
ugliness is fine.
正しさのその先で
Beyond what is right,
君と手を取りたい
I want to take your hand.
思い出せない大切な記憶
Precious memories I can't recall,
言葉にならない
feelings that cannot be expressed
ここにある想い
here in words.
もしかしたら
Perhaps,
perhaps,
それだけで
with just that,
この心は伝えてる
this heart is conveying.
もしかしたら
Perhaps,
perhaps,
君に気付いてと
hoping you'll notice,
今もその胸を
even now, my chest
打ち鳴らす
keeps beating.
なんで泣いてるのと聞かれ
When asked why I'm crying,
答えれる
I can answer.
涙なんかじゃ
Tears alone,
僕ら出会えたことの意味には
cannot keep up with the meaning
まるで追いつかない
of our encounter.
この身一つじゃ
This one body alone
足りない叫び
is not enough to cry out.
君の手に触れた時にだけ
Only when I touched your hand,
震えた心が合ったよ
my heart trembled and connected.
意味をいくつ越えれば
How many meanings must we overcome
僕らは辿り着けるのかな
to reach our destination?
愚かさでいい
Foolishness is fine,
見にくさでいい
ugliness is fine.
正しさのその先で
Beyond what is right.
小さなその先で 君と生きてきた
Beyond that small place, I've lived with you.
はあ。
Haa.
わー、皆さんこんにちは！
Wow, hello, everyone!
おはようございます、こんにちは、こんばんは。
Good morning, afternoon, evening.
皆さん、お元気ですか？
How are you guys doing?
良いですね。
Good, good.
皆さんは奇跡的に保存されてますか？ 喋れない。
Are you all miraculously preserved? I can't talk.
皆さんは奇跡的に保存されてますか？
Are you all miraculously preserved?
やった！
Yay!
聞こえるよー。イナ、ワワワ！
I can hear you guys. Yay, yay, Ina, wa, wa, wa!
はーい、皆さんにお会いできて嬉しいです。
Hi, good to see you guys.
私の誕生日ライブへようこそ！
Welcome to my birthday live!
今年も間に合ったね！
We made it in time this year!
行こう！
Let's go!
そしてもちろん、忘れないでね、話したり、
And of course, don't forget to, you know, talk about it,
スクリーンショットを撮ったり、みんなとシェアしたりするのを、
take screenshots, share it with everyone using the hashtag.
このハッシュタグを使ってね。やった！
Over here. Yeah!
そうすれば、私も皆さんが配信を見ながら
So that I can also, you know, read what you guys have
思ったことを読めるからね。
thought about while watching the stream and stuff.
ええ、もちろん、どこにいるのか、話そうか？
And yeah, of course, you know, let us talk about, uh,
どこにいるんだろう？
where are we? Where are we?
ドアを通り抜けたらいきなりここに 着いちゃったんだ。
I just went through a door and suddenly we ended up in this...
何だろう、まるで絵本の中にいるみたい。
I don't know, it almost looks like we're inside a storybook.
どこにいるか全然わからないけど、まあいいや。
I have no idea where we are, but you know what?
とにかく楽しもう！
We're going to roll with it, 'cause that's what we do.
そしてもちろん、忘れてはいけないのが…
And of course, let us not forget...
服も変わったよ！
My clothes also changed!
見て！可愛いかな？
Look! Do I look cute?
おお、たたたた。
Oh, ta ta ta.
わあ、もちろん、この全てのディテールを見てよ、
Wow, and of course, you know, look at all the details,
私のひらひらが長くなった。
my flaps have gotten longer.
ええと、このかっこいいガントレットがあるんだ。
Um, I have this cool gauntlet now.
これ見て！
Look at this!
わあ、まるで騎士みたい。
Wow, I feel like a knight.
悪をすべて打ち倒せる気がする。
I feel like I can defeat all evil.
そしてもちろん、私の、何だろう、
And of course, I got my, I don't know,
3本のガラスペンが後ろにあるの。
three glass pens behind me.
わあ、これが私の武器かな。
Wow, I wonder if this is my weapon.
ガラスペンで人を突けるよ。
Can poke people with my glass pens.
そしてドレスの全てのディテールを見て、
And all the details on the dress,
美しくない？
isn't it beautiful?
そして見て、私のスカートは実は たこダチでできてるんだ！
And look, my skirt is actually made out of takodachis!
うー。
Ooh.
そうだよ。
That's right.
もちろん、もうわかるよ、みんなが
I know also, I can already see it, you know, you guys are going,
ああ、イナだ、私だ、私だ
Oh, Ina, that's me, that's me.
でも、見てこの美しい、美しい衣装を。
But yeah, look at this beautiful, beautiful outfit.
もちろん、この素晴らしい、素晴らしい衣装をデザインしてくれた
Um, of course, I gotta thank Kuroushi Papa for designing
黒星パパに感謝しないとね。
this wonderful, wonderful outfit.
黒星パパありがとう！
Thank you, Kuroushi Papa.
いつも最高の、最高の衣装を作ってくれるからね。
You're always the best, best in making the outfit.
だからね。
So, yeah.
色々と話したいことはあるけど、今日は誕生日だし、
But you know, I want to talk about a lot of things, but it is
ここで楽しむつもりだよ。
my birthday and I'm going to go have fun around here.
どこにいるか分からないけど、探検して
I don't know where we are, but you know, I'm going to go
どこに着くか見てみるよ。
look around and see where we end up.
どうなるかな。
We'll see.
分かんない。何か楽しいことを
I don't know. Maybe we'll find
見つけられるかもしれないけど、
something fun to do, but yeah, you know,
うん、じゃあ、みんな、また会おうね。バイバイ。
I guess I'll see you guys around. Take care.
あ、ここどこだ？
Oh, what is this place?
分かんない。食べ物あるかな？うーん。
I don't know. Do they have food around here? Hmm.
か
Huh?
え、え？
Huh? Huh?
あ、アッキー先輩じゃないですか！？
Oh, Akki Senpai, isn't it you!?
あ、い、イナ！
Ah, I-Ina!
イナ！
Ina!
え、なんで石になってたんですか？
Huh? Why did you turn into stone?
わかんない！何か、鍵があったような
I don't know! I felt like there was a key,
気がした、気づいたらこの
but when I noticed, I was like this.
持ってたけど
I had it.
はい
Yes.
どこここ？
Where is this place?
私も知らないんです。
I don't know either.
イナも知らないの？
You don't know either, Ina?
はい。
Yes.
なんか急に、なんかドアにぽってしたら
Suddenly, when I touched the door,
衣装もこれになったし、ここ
my outfit became this, and this place...
ああ、そうだ。
Ah, that's right.
イナちゃん可愛い！
Ina-chan is so cute!
ちっちゃいしょ？
It's small, right?
可愛い！
Cute!
そうですね。
That's right.
可愛いでしょう？
It's cute, isn't it?
めっっちゃ可愛い！
So, so cute!
ウィンクして、ウィンクして！
Wink for me, wink!
可愛い、可愛い！
Cute, cute!
ありがとう。いや、でもここ、なんか
Thank you. But it's a completely unknown place,
全然知らない場所ってアッキー先輩がいて、なんか嬉しいな。
and Akki Senpai is here, so I'm happy.
簡単そう！
Looks easy!
えー、アキノ先輩、このね、スリーディーの姿で
Akino Senpai, I'm actually happy
いなとこうやって会えてるのは実は嬉しい。
to meet Ina in this 3D form.
嬉しい。
I'm happy.
嬉しい。実は私、あの、アッキー先輩と
I'm happy. Actually, I've always wanted
いつか、あの、歌ったり踊ったりやりたかったんです。
to sing and dance with Akki Senpai someday.
え、じゃあもしかして一緒に今日は歌えるの？
Oh, so maybe we can sing together today?
いいんですか？
Is that okay?
歌おう！
Let's sing!
やった！嬉しい！
Yay! I'm happy!
じゃあ、どの曲がいいかな？
So, what song should we sing?
うんうんうんうん。
Hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm.
ま、ホロライブの曲もあるしね、色々。
Well, there are Hololive songs too, you know, various ones.
そうですね。でもなんか
That's right. But somehow...
先輩の曲の中で一番一番好きな曲は
Among your songs, the one I love the most
やっぱりあの曲ですね。
is that song.
え、あれ？
Huh, that one?
あれですね。
That one, right?
ああ、あれ？
Ah, that one?
え、でもわかんない、言ってくんないと。
Huh, but I don't know, if you don't tell me.
あれですよね。
It's that one, right?
アッキー先輩が、こう
Akki Senpai...
ああ、あ、あ、ああ、あ、あ、あ
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
見れる
I can see it.
ちょっとセクシー
A little sexy.
セクシーダンス？
Sexy dance?
セクシーダンスはいっぱい、あるよ。
There are lots of sexy dances.
あ、いっぱいじゃないか。
Ah, not lots.
でも、でもなんか、アッキー先輩だったらこの曲。
But, if it's Akki Senpai, then this song.
じゃあ、今日は一緒にシャルイース。
So, today, shall we sing "Shal-We-Ees" together?
いいんですか？
Is that okay?
歌おう、イナ！
Let's sing, Ina!
はい。よろしくお願いします。
Yes. I look forward to it.
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
シャルイース。イナとこうやって歌うのもね、
Shal-We-Ees. It's nice to sing with Ina like this,
初めてだもんね
This is the first time, isn't it?
ライブの機会があまりなくて
I haven't had many opportunities for live performances.
確かに
Indeed.
やっと、やっと、嬉しいです！
Finally, finally! Thank you! I'm so happy!
では、アキロゼの
So, so, Akirose's...
シャールイスはアキロゼの国の
Shaluis is, after all,
伝承歌
a traditional song from Akirose's country.
イナさんの助けになることが
So, something might happen that can help Ina,
あるかもしれないですし
and I hope we can sing together and gain power.
一緒に歌ってパワーを
Yes, let's do our best.
つけてもらいたいですね
Okay, please take care of me.
はい、頑張ろう！
I'm so nervous!
はい、よろしくお願いします
Okay.
ドキドキする！
Okay, then, let's go.
はい
This way, this way, this way, this way, this way.
では、行きましょうか
Yes.
こっち、こっち
Alright.
はい
Okay, let's do our best!
よし
Yes.
じゃあ、頑張るぞ！
Kontasu Hallelujah on Shaluis
はい
Animiita Botimay Juurix
コントアス ハレルヤ オンシャールイス
Sekloqs Oknoh Klesstein Okaitin
アニミータ ボッティマイ ジューリクス
Hapluamukiru Shalubee Illu
セクロックス オークノー カレステイン オカイティン
Yanii Tinireu Midasuku Chuu
ハプルアムキル シャルーベーイル
Degitta Berinas Dikaulia
ヤニイ ティニレウミダスクチュウ
Nisui Deenas Wena Awiteikas
デギッタベリナスディーカウリーア
Tinivoras Morov Fuwa Hapuawa
ニースイ ディーナスウェナアウイテイカス
Kontasu Hallelujah Wan Shaluis
ティニーヴァラースモローフハーアハープワア
Animuwita Potimaiti Luriks
コンタス ハレリア ウォンシャールイス
Haluvia Tu Juria
アニミータポティマイ ジューリクス
Kontas Jurias Tou Kias Juria
ハルウイアトゥジューリア
Kontasu Hallelujah Wan Shaluis
コントスジュリアス トウキアスジューリア
Animuwita Potimaiti Luriks
コンタス ハレリア ウォンシャールイス
Haluvia Tu Juria
アニミータポティマイジューリクス
Sekloqs Oknoh Klesstein Okaitin
ハルウイアトゥジューリア
Hapluamukiru Shalubee Illu
セクロックスオークノーカレステインオカイティン
Sekloqs Oknoh Klesstein Okaitin
エトゥナリガリ ビディア
E, tu na ri ga ri bi di a
パラトスター ルミア ディスロモ
Para to star lu mi a di slo mo
クナズウィニア ニナイジュリ
Ku na zu wi ni a ni na i ju ri
ナレラス ムオコロロ
Na le la s mu o ko ro ro
デリラル ピプル
De li la lu pi pu ru
ナオタムル ファルマ インピラレマム セルフィ
Na o ta mu ru fa ru ma in pi ra re ma mu se ru fri
オノマド ワニロ ウダルネ
O no ma do wa ni ro u da ru ne
リナウィア ソロメ デカント ミラリラ
Li na wi a so ro me de kan to mi ra ri ra
あああ
Aaa
ハフェイン ダシミヤ
Ha fe in da si mi ya
ビモラシャ ロニコニャ
Bi mo ra sha ro ni ko nya
イミフオ イプロポメオナ
I mi fu o i pu ro po me o na
ミモラシェ ロララ
Mi mo ra she ro ra ra
コンドハレリヤ オシャルミス
Kon do ha re ri ya o sha ru mi su
アミムニタ フォキマイジュニ
A mi mu ni ta fo ki ma i ju ni
シクオクノ クレシナ ケイジン
Si ku o ku no ku re si na kei ji n
アボアニ ユキル シャルブレイル
A bo a ni yu ki ru sha ru bu re i ru
マルペセン トモラテカンフォ
Ma ru pe se n to mo ra te kan fo
デミゴイナス モロフロ
De mi go i na su mo ro hu ro
ディミゴヤス モロフア
Di mi go ya su mo ro fu a
プーアア
Pu u a a
荒らされ
Plundered,
滅びゆく歌
a song fading into ruin.
けものとなり時を切り
Becoming a beast, cutting through time,
奪い去る蟻の調べ
the melody of ants stealing it away.
輪廻の刻足り
It is the moment of reincarnation.
嫉妬羽ばたく闇
Envy takes flight in the darkness,
黒いか白から
from black or white.
諍い遠く聞き
Hearing the distant strife,
声甘い記録だね
a voice, a sweet record.
儚くささめく黒い羽
Fleeting, whispering black wings,
あの声が壊れための
that voice, for a broken eye.
有るまぼろ
an existing illusion.
黒い羽、あの歌が
Black wings, that song...
造りまどろみ
creating a slumber.
有るまぼろしいみ
There is an illusory meaning.
新たなせ
A new beginning,
凍り合う歌
a song of frozen encounters.
悪夢な舞う
The nightmares dance,
冷える
It gets cold.
虚ろ断ち切る詞が
The words that cut through emptiness,
行く紅い森から
from the red forest we walk through.
忌むべく穢れ孕む
Bearing loathsome defilement,
弱い思い
weak thoughts,
はがれる
fall away.
黒い花
Black flowers,
あの声が
and that voice,
祈りの地が
The land of prayer
荒るまま
remains as it is.
黒い花
Black flowers,
あの歌が
and that song,
残月の日が
The day of the lingering moon
荒るまま
remains as it is,
冷える
and grows cold.
最果て越える
Crossing to the very end,
壊れたとき
when it broke.
人夢
A human dream,
繰り返り
repeating.
わかる雪
The snow understands,
許されざる音
an unforgivable sound,
花
the flowers,
慈雨
and the merciful rain.
秘密の黄昏に
In the secret twilight,
君の手を取った
I took your hand.
イニシエのバラード
An ancient ballad,
繰り返すように
as it repeats,
紡ぐロマンス
weaving a romance.
君のことをいつも歌いたい
I always want to sing about you.
悲しい夜も
Even on sad nights,
温もり通して
through warmth,
愛を見つけて
I find love.
いなきくが咲いてた
The Ina kiku bloomed,
白い月輝いてた
the white moon was shining.
君の囁きで始まるよ
It begins with your whisper,
永久の storia
an eternal storia.
storia
水の中
In the water,
静か沈んでいく
slowly sinking.
懐かしい恋の物語
A nostalgic love story.
光と影の中から
From light and shadow,
愛しさは生まれて
love is born.
還る
It returns.
Come to me, Astoria, 君の目を見てた
Come to me, Astoria, I was looking into your eyes
My new dream, a savior, その腕の中で
My new dream, a savior, within those arms
恋人のささやき、星屑の散った
Lover's whispers, scattered stardust
いにしえへのバラード、泉を満たして風は
A ballad to ancient times, filling the fountain, the wind
いにしえ
Ancient times
優しい歌を、君と歌いたい
I want to sing a gentle song with you
五月の月が今ここに在る
The May moon is here now
恋の歌が今宵響くから
Because a love song echoes tonight
冷たい胸を温めてみろ
Try to warm that cold heart
心を、愛のストーリを
My heart, a story of love
あれ？
Huh?
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
あ、大丈夫？
Oh, are you okay?
大丈夫
I'm okay.
動ける！
I can move!
やったー！やったー！
Yay! Yay!
動けるようになったで！
We can move now!
動ける！動ける！
We can move! We can move!
よかったー！
That's good!
動けるようになったで！
We can move now!
動ける！やったー！
We can move! Yay!
いつものやつだ
It's the usual.
ええ？
Huh?
うわー
Wow!
動ける！どうぞ！
We can move! Alright!
何で石になってたんですか？
Why were we turned to stone?
なんでだっけ？
Why was it again?
なんかねー
Well...
なんか見たよね？
We saw something, right?
なんかねー
Something...
なんかいたんだよなー。
There was something there, wasn't there?
翼が
Wings...
生えてたかな。
Did it have them?
なんかねー
Something...
龍っぽかったかな？
Did it look like a dragon?
龍？
A dragon?
あー、ドラゴン？
Ah, a dragon?
ドラゴンだったかな？
Was it a dragon?
龍っぽかったかな？龍っぽかったな。
Looked like a dragon? It looked like a dragon.
いやあ、分かんない。
Nah, I don't know.
ちょっと覚え
I kinda remember...
分かんない。
I don't know.
覚えてない。
I don't remember.
ごめんごめん。
Sorry, sorry.
覚えてないけど
I don't remember, but...
あ、そういえば
Oh, by the way,
そういえば、イナちゃん
Speaking of which, Ina-chan,
はい。
Yes.
あなた誕生日じゃない？
It's your birthday, isn't it?
あれ？
Huh?
そうです、誕生日です！
That's right, it's my birthday!
おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
いやあ、大好きな二人と一緒って嬉しい。
It makes me so happy to be with my two favorites.
イエーイ！イエーイ！
Yay! Yay!
なんかイナちゃんとね、私とね、
Ina and I actually debuted around the same time.
一か月ぐらい。
About a month apart.
そう、一か月ぐらいだったからなんかもう同期みたいだね。
Yeah, about a month apart, so we're like同期.
同期！あ、イナ！
同期! Ah, Ina!
えへへ！同期みたいな感じだから。
We're like同期!
えへへへへへへ。嬉しい。
Yeah, it's nice!
嬉しい。そうですね。
Yes, it is nice!
でも、シシロンと歌う機会があんまりなくて。
But it's rare to get a chance to sing with Shishiro.
今回なんか、いや、いつかワタメ先輩と
So it's like, I want to sing with Senpai and Shishiro.
シシロンと歌いたいなって！やっと！
I want to sing! It's finally happening!
セットでいいですか？
A set? That's great!
嬉しい！ね！嬉しい！
Yeah! I'm happy!
嬉しい、嬉しい！二人の歌声めちゃめちゃ大好き、大好き、大好きなのです。
Happy, happy, happy! I love your singing voice so much!
嬉しい！ありがとう。
So happy! Thank you!
いなもう、大大大好きだよ。
I love, love, love, love you!
ううう。いや、私が好きだから。
I love you more.
いやいや、ワタメのが好きだから。
No, I love you more!
違う、私のほうが好きだから。
ワタメちゃんのほうが好きだから。
No, I love you the most!
いや、ボタちゃんの方が好きなから。
どっちが好きなの？イナ？
Which one do you like more, Ina?
どっちが好きなの？二人大好き！
I love both of you!
大好き！
I love you all!
あ、でもイナちゃん、なんか服が可愛くなってる？
But Ina, your outfit has become so cute!
そうですね、なんかドアがあって、ドアをぴょんとしたらこの衣装になりました。
That's right, I touched a door and turned into this outfit.
えー！可愛い！似合ってる。
Wow, so cute! It suits you!
よく見たらさ、タコタチ！あ、ね。
If you look closely, there are Takodachi!
タコダチいっぱいいるんですよ、これ。いっぱいおるんだよな。
There are lots of Takodachi!
靴も。靴もタコダチね。そう、タコダチなの可愛くない？
They're on your shoes too, Takodachi!
おしゃれだね。ね、いいな。
Stylish! It's good!
いや、でも嬉しいこの。もう、ううううううううう！嬉しい！うううう！
Oh, but I'm so happy. I'm so, so happy. I can't express it.
やっと言えたか分かんない！嬉しい！嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
こちらこそだよ。ワタメ、え、あなたちょっと時間があれじゃないの？
The same to you! Watame, you have somewhere to be, right?
え、もう時間？やばいやばい。
Oh, is it time already? Oh no, oh no!
え？あ、もう行かなきゃかも。
Huh? I have to go already!
あ、ボタちゃん、収録をあなた、あるんじゃないの？
Botan, you have a recording, don't you?
やばいやばい。飛行機乗らなきゃ。
Oh no, oh no! I have to catch a flight!
ちょっと飛行機乗って！
You have to get on the plane!
イナまたね！ありがとうね！
Ina, you have to go now!
ね、タコダチ！ありがとうね。
Yeah, Takodachi! Thank you!
ありがとうね！バイバイ！
Thank you! Bye-bye!
バイバイ！なんか、なんかおるぞ。なんだあれ？
Bye-bye! Someone's there, what is it?
なんだこれ？
What's that?
気になるな。急げ急げ！
I'm curious. Hurry, hurry!
ああ、急がなきゃ。
I have to hurry!
はあ。
Ah...
That was so fun! Uuu, I got to finally sing with Shishiron.
And of course with Watame Senpai. I'm so, so happy.
You know...
Did they say they saw something like a Takodachi?
But, after all this, I'm kinda getting sleepy.
So I'm just going to take a small nap, okay?
I'm going to take a small nap. So...
Okay.
Yeah.
[音楽再生中]
[Music Playing]
家の片隅で。
In the corner of home.
空間の片隅で。
In the corner of space.
時代の片隅で。
In the corner of era.
太陽の片隅で。
In the corner of sun.
心の片隅で。
In the corner of heart.
過去の片隅で。
In the corner of past.
世界の片隅で。
In the corner of world.
今の片隅で。
In the corner of now.
全ての片隅で。
In the corner of all.
音のない大地に 恋の歌響けば
If a love song echoes across the silent earth,
狂い出す歯車
The gears start spinning wildly,
止められぬ定めが
an unstoppable fate
はじけた 呼びかえる
burst open and called out.
いま イニシエより
Now, from ancient times,
世紀は開くの
a new era begins.
恋目覚めた
Love has awakened.
傷の萌え求めて
Seeking the budding wounds,
炎は飛び散る
the flames scatter.
儚いと再生
Transient and reborn,
けだかき君の呪縛
your noble curse.
家の片隅で。
In the corner of home.
空間の片隅で。
In the corner of space.
時代の片隅で。
In the corner of era.
太陽の片隅で。
In the corner of sun.
心の片隅で。
In the corner of heart.
過去の片隅で。
In the corner of past.
今の片隅で。
In the corner of now.
全ての片隅で。
In the corner of all.
透き通る魂
A transparent soul,
嘘もなく気高く
without lies, noble,
現在を抱えて
embracing the present,
未熟な恋もとむ
an immature love seeks.
愚かさ突き上がり
Folly surges up,
いま 独り照らす
now shining alone,
とき重ねた
the time we spent together.
傷の行方
The whereabouts of wounds,
両手で抱きしめた
I embraced with both hands.
終わりと始まり
End and beginning,
遠とき君の記憶
your distant memories.
家の片隅で。
In the corner of home.
空間の片隅で。
In the corner of space.
時代の片隅で。
In the corner of era.
太陽の片隅で。
In the corner of sun.
心の片隅で。
In the corner of heart.
過去の片隅で。
In the corner of past.
全ての片隅で。
In the corner of all.
絆を求めて
Seeking bonds,
炎を飛ばす
making flames fly.
硬いとさえさえ
Even if it's hard,
蹴飛ばす君の呪縛
I'll kick away your curse.
絆の行方を
The whereabouts of our bond,
両手で抱きしめた
I embraced with both hands.
終わりと始まり
End and beginning,
遠き君の記憶
your distant memories.
繋がりを縛る輪を描き
Draw a circle that will bind
全ての暗く憎むべき心を。
all the dark, dark, hateful mind.
欺く輪を描き
Draw a circle, that will fool
全ての暗く憎むべき掟を。
all the dark, dark, hateful rules.
解き放てないものを
You don't tear out
引き裂いてはいけない。
what you can't unlock.
あなたの心だけが知っているから、
For only your heart can know,
ひび割れから始まり、あなたは知る
You begin by your crack and know
あなたの肉欲的な色を。
your carnal color.
解き放てないものを
You don't tear out
引き裂いてはいけない。
what you can't unlock.
あなたの心だけが知っているから。
For only your heart can know.
Dún an doras, is mo leanaí
Close the door, my child
Déanaim codladh a rún.
Sleep, my dear.
Seoithín, seoithó, a leanbh móir
Hush, oh, my big child
Ar maidin, go luath a bhíodh
In the morning, early I'd be
Ar druidim na súl.
As eyes are closing.
Dia duit, a chailín díofa
Hello, lost girl,
ag maireachtáil ar thóir óir.
living in pursuit of gold.
自分を傷つける必要なんてない。
You don't need to hurt yourself.
自分を傷つけることしか知らない。
You only know how to hurt yourself.
私はあなたを傷つけない。
I will never hurt you.
自分を傷つける必要なんてない。
You don't need to hurt yourself.
自分を傷つけることしか知らない。
You only know how to hurt yourself.
Dún an doras, is mo leanaí
Close the door, my child
Déanaim codladh a rún.
Sleep, my dear.
時の揺り籠で
In the cradle of time,
冷たい夢を見る
I see cold dreams.
君が歌ってくれた
The gentle lullaby
優しい優しい子守唄
that you sang for me.
君が望んだのは 終る世界
What you wished for was an ending world.
私が望むのは 世界の終わり
What I desire is the end of the world.
選ばれし声は 迷い
The chosen voice is lost.
哀れを歌う悲しみは喜びに
Sadness sings pity, transforming into joy.
苦しみを希望に
Pain turns into hope.
朽ち果てて 受け入れずに
Decaying, without acceptance.
君は朽ちていくの
You are withering away.
虚に抱いて この世界もはや君だけ
Embracing emptiness, in this world, it's just you.
もういいの
I'm done.
交わらない
We don't connect.
巡り巡る命は
Revolving lives are
この手で
in these hands.
安らぎと 祝歌を
Peace and celebratory songs,
終わらせない
I won't let them end.
潰れない 虚しい願いは
Uncrushable, empty wishes
虚しさだけを 残して
only leave behind emptiness.
始まる
It begins.
哀れを歌う悲しみは喜びに
Sadness sings pity, transforming into joy.
苦しみを希望に 朽ちていく
Pain turns into hope. Decaying.
永遠に朽ちない定めを
An eternal, undecaying destiny.
今解き放つ
Now, unleash it.
君が望んだのは
What you wished for
あなたの未来
was your future.
彼が望んだのは
What he wished for
償い続けたのは
was to keep atoning.
優しい笑顔
Just a kind smile,
それだけなのに
that's all, and yet...
終わらない 歌声を
Transform the endless singing
希望に変えて
into hope.
叫び続けた
I kept shouting,
滅びる定めなら
"If it's our destiny to perish,"
軋む未来の
Let the voice of the
声を響け
creaking future resonate.
巡り巡る世界に
In the revolving world,
安らぎと
peace and
祝歌を
celebratory songs,
光を
light,
定めを
destiny.
闇を解き放て
Unleash the darkness.
歌声を 希望に変えて
Turn singing into hope,
叫び続けて
keep shouting.
君は朽ちていくの
You are withering away.
軋む未来の
Let the voice of the
声を響け
creaking future resonate.
君が望んだのは
What you wished for,
俺が望んだのは
what I wished for,
残された声は嘆き
The remaining voice grieves,
君を思いながら
thinking of you.
独り君のために
I sing alone,
歌う
for you.
独り君のために
Alone, for you,
歌う
I sing.
巡り巡る命は
Revolving lives are
この手で
in these hands.
安らぎと祝歌を
Peace and celebratory songs,
滅びない
imperishable.
定めを この未来
Destiny, this future,
君とならどこまでも
with you, to the ends of the world.
朽ちない
Undying.
僕らのして飛ばし作る行為は
Our acts of flying and creating
光を誘う為の
Are to invite the light
光を誘う為の、光のそこに
Are to invite the light. In the depths of light,
光のそこに眠れる
Sleeping in the depths of light.
ベイ、大丈夫？
Bae, are you okay?
あぁ、私のナイト、
Ah, my knight,
やっと来てくれた。
finally you've come.
もう、マジで100年ぐらい待ったんすけど。
Seriously, I waited like 100 years, man.
何してんすか？
What took you so long?
100？100年？
100? 100 years?
ちょっと待って、ちょっと待って。
Wait, hold on, hold on.
えっと、Google、ネズミってどれぐらい生きるんだっけ？
Google, how long does a rat live?
もう、もう、筋肉がね。
Man, oh my, oh my muscles.
あぁ、固まっちゃったから。
Ah, they're so rigid from being stuck as a statue.
でもありがとうね、助けてくれて。
But thank you so much for saving me.
大丈夫。ほら、
Don't worry, you know what?
イナのヒーローが助けに来てくれたじゃん。
Ina the hero is here to save you.
ああ、ありがとう。
Oh, thank you.
うん。邪悪なドラゴンを倒したからね。
Yeah, we defeated the evil dragon.
せやった。ネズミを。よくもそんなこと。
Serves them right! How dare they?
みんな見たかわかんないけど、
I don't know if you guys saw,
邪悪なドラゴンがいたからね。
but there was an evil dragon here.
ざまぁみろ。よくもそんなこと。
Serves them right! How dare they?
大丈夫？大丈夫？
Are you okay? Are you okay?
オールグッド、サンキュー、サンキュー。
I'm all good. Thank you, thank you.
うん。じゃあ元気になったことだし、
Yeah, now that you're all well,
あれ言って。
you may as well say a thing.
え？
Eh?
あれだよ、あれ。
Say the thing, you know? The thing.
あれ？
What thing?
ほら、今日スペシャルデーみたいな
You know, like today is
なってる日？
a special day.
あ！そう！今日が、えっと、
Oh! Yeah, today is, um...
姫が助けられた日。
Today is the day that the princess has been saved.
どうもありがとう。ありがとう。
Thank you very much, thank you.
拍手、拍手。はい、あざます、あざますね。
Yes, I understand, I understand.
違う違う違う違う。べべ、べべ。
No, no, no, no, Bae. Bae, Bae.
あ？
Huh?
違うの。
No.
何の日、えっと、
What day is when, um,
紫のが生まれた日。
this purple one come to be?
あ！そっか！そっちの方探してるのか。
Oh! I see. You're looking for that one.
うんうんうん。
Yeah, yeah, okay, okay, okay.
イナちゃん、ハッピーバースデー！
Ina-chan! Happy Birthday!
イェイ！今日は来てくれて
Yay! Thanks for joining me
ありがとうね、べー。
today, Bae.
誘ってくれてありがとう。
Thank you for inviting me.
嬉しかった。
I'm so happy.
楽しかった。
It was so fun.
うん、そう楽しかった。踊れて、
It was so fun. To dance with you,
歌えて。
sing with you.
最高、最高。
It's the best, it's the best.
うん。あの、
Yes. I just wanted to say,
新しい衣装めっちゃ可愛いなって。
your new outfit is so cute.
あ、ありがとう。気に入ってくれた？
Oh, thank you. You like it?
え、めっちゃ可愛い。やばい。
It's so cute. Oh my God.
これはね、えっと、
It's, it's called...
何ていう衣装だっけ？
What's the outfit called?
勇者。勇者。
Yuusha. Yuusha.
イェス。
Yes.
そう、ヒーローっぽい。
That's right, I look like a hero, right?
ヒーローだよね。
You do look like a hero.
マイヒーロー。
My hero.
おお。あ、べー。
Ooh. Ah, Bae.
そしてミスタースクイクス、
And Mr. Squeaks, thanks for
べーのところまで導いてくれてありがとう。
leading me to Bae.
サンキュー、メン。グッジョブ。
Thanks, man. You did great.
ハイタッチ。
High five.
あ、あ。
Oh.
マジで彼がいなかったら
Man, if it wasn't for him,
永久に像だった。
I'd be stuck as a statue forever.
頭振りすぎると飛んでっちゃうよ。
Don't shake your head too much, he's gonna fly off.
そう、くっついてる。
Yeah, he sticks to it.
ふふっ。あぁ。
Oh no!
OK。オールグッド。
There we go. It's all good.
でも、うん、ベ、来てくれてありがとう。
But yeah, thank you, Bae, for joining us
助けてくれて。
and saving me.
楽しかった。
So fun.
えっと、あなたはこれで旅を
Well, I think, are you still going
続けて、
on your journey after this?
私はヒーロー。
I am a hero.
ねぇ、助けなきゃいけない
Girl, I gotta go see
お姫様たちに会いに行かなきゃ。
all the princesses that I gotta save in the world.
え、ちょっと！
Excuse me!
え？
Huh?
私だけじゃないわ！
It wasn't just me!
よし、行くぞ！
Alright, let's go!
あああ！
Aaaah!
あああああ！
まあ、いいか。
Well, that's that.
次のお姫様だ！行くぞ！
On to the next princess! Let's go!
何百何千何万の夜を越えて
Many days spent in fairy tales,
ようやく辿り着いた物語の果て
seems to have arrived at the end.
そこで僕らは見てきた
The proof we have seen
遠い日の僕らの足跡
are our footprints from a distant past.
古びた地図を広げて
The voice still can't place
踏み出したその一歩
right on this field.
安らぎのベールを置き去りに
Shadows of manifested
全てを救うため旅立つ勇者
pain and loss.
あなたとの小さな旅の記憶
There was a hero who took out all foes.
あの物語にもうページはない
No more pages left in that story.
僕らの英雄は深い眠りにつく
Our hero goes into slumber deep,
皆のために平和のベールを残し
Leaving behind the veil of peace for all.
森の床から花々を救いながら
Saving the flowers from the forest floor.
時の流れは容赦なく消し去る
The flow of time erases without mercy,
そして全ての記憶と用途を蝕む
And erodes all memories and use.
今生に残された痕跡さえも
Even the traces left in life for now.
失われたものは、時間は無益だ
Lost thing is time is useless,
それでも私はあなたの希望を全て保つ
And yet I keep all your hopes,
全ての言葉と願い、勇気を見つけるでしょう
All the words and wishes, courage you'll find,
心の中にずっと、今もなお
said throughout inside me and even now
私の心で、生き続けよう
in my heart, keep living through.
誠実な物語が分かち合われるだろう
A honest story will be shared,
同じ道、止めるものはない
the same path and nothing more to stop
そうあるべきだったのに、ふと疑問に思った
The way it should have been, but suddenly I was wondering
力強い剣を振るう英雄たち
all those heroes swinging their mighty swords.
なぜ彼らは虚空から現れるのか、知りたい
Why do they come out of the void, I want to find out
今いる場所まで。もし旅に出たら
until they were right now. If I engage in the journey
私たちはまた出会えるかもしれない
we might have both again.
もうあなたの隣を歩いていないけれど
Though I am no longer walking next to you,
いつか真実を見つけ出す
one day I will find the truth.
この物語の終わりはどこ？
Where's the end in this story?
今、新しい物語を始めよう
Start a new story now.
この旅ではいつもあなたのそばに
Always by your side for this journey.
物語は獣のもの、その希望を
Stories are of the beast, keep those hopes
永遠に、ずっと、ずっと、ずっと
Forever, ever, ever, ever,
今、全てが見えている
I'm seeing them all now.
そして新しい物語が広がる
And a new story unfolds,
一人で踏み出した旅へと
into a journey that alone I set out to.
立ち寄った町の住民たちに会った
I met the locals of every town I stopped into.
彼らは皆、あなたが誰であったかを思い出す
They are all recalling the person that you were.
揺るぎない優しさが語られている
Unwavering kindness is spoken of you,
何をするにもクールに振る舞い
acting all cool in everything you do.
あちこちで、あなたは見つけるだろう
Here and there you can find
散らばったシンボル、戦いを現す
scattered symbols around, manifesting battles
平和のために勝利した戦いを
we won for peace.
そしてそれさえも私にとっては夢だった
And even that was a dream for me,
だからいつか、孤独になっている自分に気づく
so one day I would have found myself along becoming lonely.
そして私は彼らに、私たちの旅の
And I recall to them every moment
あらゆる瞬間を
of our journey
この場面に残された印を見ると
when I see the signs left in these scenes.
あー あー あー えー えー えー あー あー あー
Ah ah ah eh eh eh ah ah ah
おー おー おー おー おー おー おー あー あー あー
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh ah ah ah
へー へー へー えー えー えー あー あー あー
Hey hey hey eh eh eh ah ah ah
おとぎ話の日々
Many days spent in fairy tales,
終わりが来たみたい
seems to have arrived at the end.
見てきた証拠は、
The proof we have seen,
運命が動いた瞬間だった
it was that moment our fate was moving,
旅の現在が私と共にあった
the present of the journey stayed with me.
たとえあなたの勇敢な場所が
Even if your courageous spot,
距離を忘れても
don't forget the distance.
そして私はあなたの信頼を勝ち取る
And I will win your faith,
皆が思い出せることを知っているでしょう
you know what everybody can recall.
私はあなたを私と一緒に
I will bring you on with me
未来へ連れて行く
into the future.
だから手を取って、始まるだろう
So you take your hand and I'll know it'll begin
あの時に。いつか毎日が輝く
right at that time. One day everyday shines,
瞬間が燃え上がり、あなたの影が残る
the moments ignited and us of you remain.
私の思い出は、あの頃のように輝き続ける
My reflections all those times go on as brightly shining.
私たちが今どこにいるのか
I want to find out and see where we are right now,
振り返ってみよう
looking back at us.
永遠にそびえ立ち、穏やかに私を照らす
Standing tall evermore, gently shining bright at me
音もなく
without a sound.
今、あなたを追いかける
I'm pursuing you, right now.
物語を語ろう ずっと待っているよ
I'll tell you story. I'll still be waiting
あなたが加わる英雄の物語を永遠に
for you to join me story of the hero forever.
いつまでも いつまでも
Ever, ever, ever.
始まりを知り、どうしてこうなったのか
Knowing that your beginning, how to come to be and end this
守り、安全に保つために終わりを告げる
that you protect your and keep in safety.
この芽生える線は、この旅で私と共にある
These budding lines are with me on this journey.
やったー！そして彼らはいつまでも幸せに暮らしました。
Yay! And then they lived happily ever after.
あるいは、Evermoreと言うべきでしょうか。
Or should I say, Evermore.
見てくれてありがとうね。楽しんでくれたかな？
But yeah, thank you guys for watching today. I hope you
どうだったかハッシュタグ使って教えてね。
guys enjoyed it. Make sure you, you know, tell me how
そして、もちろん、私の誕生日なので、
it was using the hashtag. And of course, since it is
誕生日なので、
my birthday,
私の誕生日グッズをみんなに紹介しないとね。
I also have to introduce some of my birthday merch to
やったー！
you guys! Yay!
今年の誕生日グッズはこれらのアイテムです。
So we have these items for, um, the birthday merch
見てね。ドドン！
this year. Let's see. Todon!
やった！見て、これが2025年の誕生日グッズだよ。
Yay, look, this is my 2025 birthday merch.
えー、いくつかグッズがあります。
Uh, we have a couple of items.
では、最初のアイテムです。次！
So, the first item. Next.
はい、最初のアイテムはリバーシブルトートバッグです。
Okay, with the first item, we have the reversible tote
両面で異なるデザインになっているので、
bag. It has a different design on each side.
外側にどんなデザインにしたいかによって、
So depending on what you feel like having on the outside,
TV先生のかわいいキービジュアルか、
you can choose between the lovely key visual by TV-sensei
もっと目立たないシンプルなデザインか選べるよ。
or a very simplified design to be more incognito.
そして、もちろん、次のもあります！次！
And of course, we have another one, so next.
タコダチの、えー、シェイカーアクリルキーホルダーです。
We have the Takodachi, uh, shaker acrylic key holder.
デザインは私が考えたんですけど、
The design, I designed myself, and I wanted it to be
持ち歩けて、こう、ちっちゃなゲームみたいに見えるように、
kind of like, you know, you can carry it around and it
振ってタコダチがシャカシャカ動くよ。
kind of seems like a little game that you can play.
すごく楽しいアイテムです。
You can shake it around and the Takodachis will shake.
そして次に、これもまた、
It's a really fun item. And then next, we also have the...
タコダチケーブルタイです。ぐちゃぐちゃな
Takodachi Cable Tie, where you can organize the messy,
ケーブルを整理できます、私みたいにね。
messy chaos that is the cables in your bag like, like me.
うん、役に立つといいな。
But yeah, I hope they're useful.
そして最後に、次の、
And last but not least, we have the next...
勇者イナ、別名二ノ前イナニス・ザ・ヒーロー、
Yusha Ina, aka Ninomae Ina'nis the Hero, this outfit,
この衣装は、私が自分をヒーローと呼んでいるもので、
I call myself the hero. It's a cute, uh, plushie,
どこにでも持ち歩けるかわいいぬいぐるみキーチェーンだよ。
uh, keychain that you can carry around everywhere.
そして、私がみんなを守るよ。お守りだね。
And I will protect you. It's a lucky charm.
あとは、もちろんフルセット購入特典があります。
But yeah, and of course, there is a full set bonus,
それは限定、または限定版のポストカードが
which is going to be a limited, or I will have a limited
手に入ります。セットを購入すれば、
edition, uh, postcard, but, uh, if you buy the set,
ポストカードも手に入ります。限定セットと限定なしセットがあるよ。
you also get the postcard. There's a limited set and a not limited set, so there's that.
そしてもちろん、スペシャルな
And, of course, we also have a special
ホロライブTCGカードもございます。
hololive TCG card with the key art.
それはお礼のようなものです
Uh, it's like a thank you bonus for
グッズのフルセットの特典です。
the complete set of the merch.
えーと、このカードは
Um, this card will only be given to
購入されたお客様にのみ
customers who purchased from the
ホロライブ公式ショップで提供されます。
hololive Production official shop.
そしてこれは推しホロメンカードで、
And this is an Oshi holomem card,
ゲーム内で1枚だけ使用できます。
which you can use only one in the game.
たくさんのルールがあります
I know there's a whole bunch of rules
ウェブサイトで確認できます。
that you can check out on the website.
残念ながら日本語版のみです。
Unfortunately, it's only the Japanese version.
日本語のテキストしかありませんが、
There's only Japanese text on it, but, you know,
これは特別な限定品です。
it's kind of like a special limited thing.
なので、持っていると良いですよ。
So, something nice to have.
はい、グッズのお知らせは以上です。
But yeah, that is it for merch announcement,
今日のライブを楽しんでいただけたでしょうか。
etc. I hope you guys enjoyed the live today.
そしてもちろん、おまけがあります。
And of course, we still have the Omake,
最後にちょっとしたNG集と
the little NG kind of snippets in the end
クレジットがありますので、お楽しみに。
and the credits. So, please look forward to that.
それではまた次回、皆さんありがとうございました！
Until next time, thank you again everyone!
残りの午前、午後を
Have a wonderful rest of the morning,
楽しんでくださいね。
afternoon or evening.
またね！バイバイ！
I'll see you guys later. Bye-bye!
Music: トライフロンティア合同会社
Music: TRI FRONTIER
すぐろーす
Suguro-su
山本こーすけ
Yamamoto Keisuke
ふじそば
Fujisoba
クックルP
Kukuru P
Sound City
小林綾彩
Kobayashi Ayaka
中山太陽
Nakayama Taiyo
堀口彩花
Horiguchi Ayaka
Filming & Planning: COVER Corp. STUDIO
SPECIAL THANKS: Takodachi
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thanks for watching everyone!
今日という特別な日を、
I'm really happy that I was able to share this
皆さんと分かち合えて本当に嬉しいです！
special day with you today!
ライブ楽しかったですか？新しい衣装はどうですか？
Did you enjoy the live? Do you like the new outfit?
へへ。
Hehe.
衣装のテーマのように、
Just like the theme of the outfit,
これからも私は、何をするにも
I would like to continue to do my bestest
最高の状態で臨みたいです！
with everything I do!
なぜなら、それが勇者のすることだから！
Because that is what a hero - Yuusha would do!
もちろん、いつも応援してくれてありがとう！
Sure. Thank you for cheering for me!
皆さんのサポートがなければ、私は
Always!! I really wouldn't be here
ここにいられなかったでしょう！
without all your support!
そしてもちろん、スタッフの皆さん、
And of course, BIG thank you to all the staff
そしてこれを実現してくれたクリエイターの
& creators that could make this happen too!
皆さんにも感謝します！皆さんの情熱には
I am always indebted to everyone's passion!
いつも感謝しています！ありがとう、そしてありがとう！
THANK YOU & THANK YOU! It's time... TO GO NEXT!!